M

Search for:     

POPULAR POSTS & PAGES

Book Layouts and Page Margins: Everything You Need to Know

The 20 Best Audiobooks on Spotify (And How to Listen)

Sample Copyright Pages \[2 FREE Templates for Your Book\]

Amazon Print on Demand

Book Disclaimers: Everything You Need to Know

The Book Fonts Guide: Everything You Need to Know About Book Typography

What Is Voice in Writing? \[Examples Included\]

How To Make A Coloring Book Using AI In 4 Easy Steps

What is Passive Voice Misuse? (Examples and Fixes)

4 Illuminating Hero’s Journey Examples From Popular Stories

TheBookDesigner.com Privacy Policy
==================================

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for TheBookDesigner.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
----------------------------------------

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

Your Access to and Control Over Information
-------------------------------------------

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

* See what data we have about you, if any.
* Change/correct any data we have about you.
* Have us delete any data we have about you.
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

Security
--------

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Registration
------------

In order to use some features this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.

Orders
------

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.

Cookies
-------

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

Sharing
-------

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

Links
-----

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

Surveys & Contests
------------------

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

Book Content Rights
-------------------

During the process of providing support or issuance of a quotation for service, partial or completed book files may be requested or transmitted to us via electronic means.  We retain no ownership over the creative work of the author or writer, and make not claims of copyright of the authors or writer’s creative work.  Works transmitted to us will be destroyed or erased upon written request.

Updates
-------

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via [our online contact form](https://www.thebookdesigner.com/contact-us/).**

Search for:  

[

](https://selfpublishingschool.clickfunnels.com/aal-2024-tickets)

Pin

0 Shares

Coaching + Publishing

Education

Writing

Formatting + Design

Freelance

Freelance Community

At **THEBOOKDESIGNER.COM,** our goal is to be your go-to resource for all things related to high-quality book design.  Whether you are a first-time author or book designer by trade, we are committed to helping you navigate self-publishing by giving you the tools and resources you need to stand out in a competitive industry. 

Navigate
--------

Free Tools & Resources
----------------------

Copyright selfpublishing.com All Rights Reserved. © 2024
